Matt Williams

1-778-268-0497 — mattinzhuhai@gmail.com www.mattwilliams.site

Highlights of Qualifications

Instructed more than 45 SGE students, yielding a 75 percent success rate.

Increased SGE customer base by 30 percent in one year.

Accomplished sales and distribution goals by executing the monthly, quarterly and annual business objectives at Columbia Distribution.

Developed Patience and Attentiveness with customers while working with ESL students and business owners in high stress environments.

Work Experience

2019–Present	Placement	Coordinator	Integrita	Immigration-	— Nanaimo	BC
2019-1 Tesem	1 lacement	Coordinator	11111001111111	- 111111111111111111111111111111111111	— mananno	\mathbf{D}

Assessing and aiding International ESL students new to Canada looking to gain entry to and succeed in University

2016–2018 | Sales/Marketing/Instructor SGE— Shenzhen China

IELTS and TOEFL Instructor working with Chinese students looking to study abroad.

Responsible for monthly marketing events and organizing public "English Corner" style speaking and learning activities.

2011–2015 | Sales and Merchandising Columbia Distribution— Seattle WA

As an on-premise salesmen, my job was to secure new business accounts and facilitate the needs of existing accounts. This was accomplished through managing inventory, expenses, territory planning and keeping a respectful dialogue with customers and inter-company departments.

Education

2018-Present | BSc in Computer Science, Vancouver Island University, Canada

Technical Skills

Programming C/C++
Automation Python, Bash
Markup HTML, CSS, SCSS, IATEX
OS Windows, Linux, Mac
Office Ms Office, Libre Office